Good morning, students.
Today we will announce,
the format of our second exam.
Students will play
the Perfect Partners group game,
to find their partner for the next round.
Based on the rankings from the last exam,
the top four students
will go to the next room one by one
to answer multiple-choice questions.
Among the remaining students, whoever wants to team up with them,
must guess their answer.
When the answers are revealed, a match means the two students successfully team up.
If multiple people choose the same student, they can choose one in return.
If no one picks or they refuse, they sit out.
The last ones left will team up freely.
We'll start with Bai Guanyu, who has the most credits.
If you could choose freely,
would you want to be first,
middle, or last in your family or group?
A. The eldest.
B. In the middle.
C. Benjamin.
Anyone willing to team up with Bai,
please stand up.
You can choose now.
Big Bai would probably pick...
the middle?
I think he'll pick the youngest.
I'm sure of it.
Because I remember Big Bai,
in our daily conversations,
he's called me his little brother before.
So I feel like he'd be
more of a big brother type.
Do you know what 'Benjamin' means?
Benjamin is the smallest.
The youngest one.
Right. So why did he call you his little brother and you think he wants to be the youngest?
No wait, he called me 'little brother',
so he's the eldest.
Right, so you should pick A.
Isn't that A?
That's C.
Right, I came here.
Because in our team,
he is the eldest.
If he were in a family,
I think he'd probably be the youngest.
And he'd be happy with that if he could switch to a different identity.
Because I talked with Big Bai a couple days ago.
We were dividing people,
into four Animal Personalities.
Big Bai said he was actually more like the lion.
But among us, he's not the type,
who insists on controlling everything himself.
So I think he'd go with the middle way.
I think he might pick B.
The middle way.
I just feel so.
Just that simple.
Right, exactly.
A man's intuition.
Right.
Everyone, please stand still and make your final choice.
Come on, let's hold this red rope together.
So excited.
So excited, Big Bai.
My heart is pounding.
My eyelids are twitching like crazy.
So nervous.
More nervous than an exam.
Please hold tight the red rope
you've chosen.
Three.
We'll depend on each other, then.
Finally, you're here.
Good thing I never gave up.
Big brother.
I'm called big brother because I'm the youngest at home.
The age gap between me and my older siblings is a bit big.
They always think of me as still a little kid.
But actually, I'm someone,
who knows exactly what I want.
Honestly, I'd want to work with both.
But,
if we're respecting the game rules,
and can only pick one.
Then I'll just be more direct about it.
Then,
whoever's hand I take,
that's who I'll pick, okay?
I pick...
Actually, I hope, if there's a chance,
in what's coming next...
Because we might not just have one performance,
I hope I get the chance
to work with everyone separately.
But this time,
I think after watching the entire show,
what touched me the most, relatively speaking,
was Xiaomeng's performance.
Maybe the two of us
have had pretty similar experiences.
Right.
So we were able,
to open up to each other,
and I'd really like to learn more about
what Xiaomeng's experience has been like.
Those who want to pick Ziyu,
please stand up.
I'll stand up as always.
Just standing.
I'm just standing.
Pick a few more.
If it doesn't work this time, I'll be left on the shelf.
I'll just wait until the very last one.
What message would Zhang Ziyu,
send in his own,
WeChat chat box?
A. To-do list.
B. Mood reflections.
C. Writing poems.
Writing poems in the chat box.
To himself...
To himself, in his own WeChat chat box.
I think it's definitely C.
That's what a poser like him will do.
Ziyu really loves
that brotherhood-and-loyalty kind of stuff.
Buddies, sworn brothers...
Freestyle rap.
I don't want to stand here,
I want to stand on the table.
They all say youth never comes twice.
I'll make everyone,
submit to me.
Then do the fist salute.
That's so hip-hop.
So rap, so underground.
I'd say it's a bit 'pretentious.'
He gives me the impression that he can really do that.
You know?
Like, melancholic,
sitting there, and writing a poem.
And you see he writes rap, right?
I think writing rap is the same thing as writing poetry.
Yeah, he could totally do that.
Right, he just puts what he wants to say into a poem.
I'd pick C too.
Because he just seems like
such a poetic person.
That gesture.
That body language.
If he doesn't pick us,
we'll pick each other.
We're just so like-minded.
The two of us,
just hugged each other.
I'll pick A.
Because I just feel it.
It's intuition.
It feels like he's a P-type person.
He's not a J-type.
He's a P.
How would a P have a to-do list?
A P would never write a to-do list.
It's precisely because I'm a P, that I know.
I'd write down the things I haven't done on that list
to remind myself.
I think I'll pick B.
Because I'm a P too.
But I feel like he is
a P wouldn't write plans.
Even though he writes rap,
I don't think he'd write poetry.
I think personal reflections are what I'd write.
So I think.
Do you write down your feelings?
When I'm in a good mood,
I'll jot down a line or two.
I think since he's a P-type, he probably does too.
Can't change it now.
Nothing can be changed.
Actually it felt pretty right.
Right.
But it's fine, we'll just stick to our principles.
Looking forward to it.
Go stand over there, okay?
I'm so nervous.
So it really is C.
So close.
Do you even get it?
I'm saying you look like the type who'd be 'pre'... write poetry.
No.
I really don't like admitting I write poetry.
But this really is something I did back in my cringey phase.
Yeah, I'll openly admit it.
Didn't expect this one.
Mingyang actually picked me.
And he even picked the right answer.
So I figured I'd just
leave it up to fate.
Right.
Then I had the two of them play rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I threw scissors.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Come on.
=Our Central Academy of Drama. -CAD Duo.
Would anyone think I'd write a to-do list?
I'm someone who doesn't even know,
where I put my clothes.
A broken heart is like shattered glass.
Well, I'm not close with Ma.
You go.
But I'd like to
get to know the classmates
I haven't really spent time with.
It's just the three of us.
Because I already know him.
Senior, finally we meet!
I wanted to get to know more people.
I already went up last round, so I won't pick anyone this round.
I'll do it.
Ma's question is this.
If the frying pan at home went missing,
why would that be?
The frying pan.
A. Ma Weixian saw it was broken,
and threw it away.
B. The old pan was stored away by Ma Weixian.
C. Ma Weixian took it to the streets of Hong Kong, China,
to pan-fry wagyu beef.
Ma Weixian took it to
the streets of Hong Kong
to pan-fry wagyu.
My first instinct is C.
It's so absurd, that it just feels like something he'd do.
No reason needed.
The other two options completely lose their appeal
next to this answer.
I'm going with C right away.
Alright, let's welcome Ma!
Three, two, one, reveal!
Awesome!
Good buddy.
How's that?
Sure.
Unbeatable!
It's mutual.
Truly mutual.
Come on, play a song,
'Writing a Poem for You.'
There's a dish I've been craving for ages,
but it's only sold in Hong Kong,
and I couldn't bring it back to the mainland,
because customs wouldn't allow it.
So I figured, since I couldn't bring the food back,
I'd just bring a pan over instead,
and after buying it there,
find a convenience store, with the pan...
It was electric, and then,
I can just pan-fry it and eat it.
Okay, so for the remaining two...
We got auto-matched successfully.
Okay.
You need to answer Chen Zhixuan's question.
If you gained one invincible talent,
what would you want most?
A. Instant amnesia.
B. Automatic empathy.
C. A born optimist.
So hard.
I think it's C.
I think it's C too.
Sir, I want to guess, I'll go with A.
I really think,
he must choose C.
Why do I feel it's A?
Get ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
Misplaced trust.
What did you all pick?
We picked C.
All picked C? Why?
Because I think you want to be happy.
Because we think B is definitely...
You're naturally very emotional and empathetic.
It's exactly because he's too emotional and empathetic,
and takes on too many emotions.
He'd want instant amnesia.
He'd want to forget those abilities.
Seriously, that's what I thought.
What about my partner?
What does that mean?
No, I'm everyone's good partner.
Right, he really gets it.
Come on, welcome everyone.
So, how do you all feel about yesterday's performance?
Pretty good.
Pretty good, satisfied with yourself?
Who's especially satisfied with themselves?
Me.
You already got fifty points. You're not satisfied?
No.
I found it really satisfying.
Really satisfying.
Who here is unsatisfied with themselves?
Unsatisfied.
You're not satisfied?
Be completely honest in how you express yourselves.
And later on, we still have a long time together.
One and a half months. Six weeks.
The whole time, I hope we all
keep communicating honestly.
Starting today,
this is our first acting class.
Acting itself, is about portraying relationships between people.
All of you yesterday gave a solo performance on stage,
But we've been emphasizing all along:
who is your scene partner?
Right? So today, with each other,
we need to find our scene partners.
Okay?
Good. Come on, let's form a circle first.
Look, there are three sets of dialogues here.
You can pick any one of them.
This is the first-and-last line.
What happened in between?
You can say four lines total.
On the right, there are these red action verbs.
Pick three from them to complete it.
I hope that in this process, you'll try as much as possible, to rely more
on the actions themselves,
and not just keep using dialogue to convey things to me. Okay?
You can go take a look now.
Go.
Each group picks one.
I'll give you ten minutes.
Which set do you want to pick?
Or do you have...
I think either A or B works for me.
Two seems a bit easier.
Two?
Sure.
How about we take the first set?
I think A is pretty good.
A is pretty good.
Right.
Which one do you want to pick?
I think the second one works better too.
The third one is that
you're in a college entrance examination scenario.
You didn't make it, and you're wondering whether to spend another year on it.
Shake hands.
Push. Pull.
Lift me up high.
What is 'lift you up high'?
Is lifting up high like this?
Can you lift me up high?
Can you even lift me?
I don't think I can.
What I had in mind was one being a pull,
and the other being a direct hug.
So in the end it's 'hold on, don't give up, '
and then pull me up,
right off the ground in one motion.
I could do this,
at first I walk away all angry,
then you grab me,
'Let's talk, okay?'
And then the two of us suddenly start a chicken fight.
Genius.
Come on, get ready.
You.
Why did you shut down?
The results are out.
I totally bombed the exam.
Right now,
I either go get a job,
or give it another year.
I really can't accept it.
I know if I keep going,
it'll be
painful, really hard.
But,
this really is my dream.
I think,
if you have a dream,
you have to chase it.
So do you want me to keep holding on?
Come on,
don't give up.
Okay, here we go.
So, what's your relationship?
Classmates.
Where are you?
What are the given circumstances?
I feel like it's in a room.
Right, a room at home.
Or a dorm.
I feel like he's in a very enclosed space,
resting all alone, having some quiet time.
Then he comes to find him.
What I'm thinking is actually, maybe more like
Zhou Guorui is leaning against,
a corner close to the door.
Because I just saw,
Ma Weixian ran over,
and turned the corner,
so it feels more like
he walks in and sees him crouching there.
Yes, exactly.
That's the scenario.
Consider it done.
But,
what I emphasized just now
was trying to use actions,
use movement to accomplish it.
You were mostly explaining things,
relying on Zhou Guorui's words,
to convey his state.
Ma Weixian over here was mostly,
just a listener.
No problem, that's fine.
But I think as we, keep going forward,
I'd hope that you two, can act more.
Building the relationship shouldn't rely on just one person's endlessly talking.
Okay, next group.
Provoking.
Let's talk, okay?
Get lost.
Come on.
If I lose, I'll apologize.
That's so 'low'.
Aren't you being childish?
Why are you still so full of yourself?
Get out of the way.
Why did you change the scene?
Why did you change the scene!
Weren't we told not to change it? Before going on stage.
I didn't see it.
I thought you were doing it.
I saw you folding stuff over there.
I...
What scene is this?
No, wait.
You were folding clothes over there. I stepped on it.
I was standing right here. You didn't look at me.
You are hurt?
Well, madam.
I held it in twice.
And then at the end, your bit.
I couldn't hold back my laughter.
So what was your first move?
Stepping or shooting with your foot?
I actually stepped on it.
I wanted to get your attention.
Come on.
Keep going after the scene.
Hurry.
Bye.
Come on.
Pretty good.
Look at their relationship.
Playing golf while walking.
Those two look more like a couple.
What couple suddenly starts a chicken fight?
One good thing about this pair...
Well, it's naturally hilarious.
His personality really comes through.
Even though you all said,
why change the scene, the stepping thing,
but the two characters, through their actions and movements,
including the chicken-fight hops and the back-and-forth jumps,
and that pesky, cheeky personality of his, really came through.
And Sun Mingyang was great too.
The way the two of them
adapted to each other was really good.
Next group.
I saw you yesterday.
You were there too?
What's up?
It's not gonna work.
No.
That's it.
Just stay put.
I feel like I can't stay any longer.
So you've made up your mind?
Just let everything take its natural course.
Let's go.
Jiang Xiaomeng,
can you lift me up high?
I don't think I can.
He's gone.
What's their relationship?
Like a couple breaking up.
I think they're buddies.
Right.
Roommates.
You both guessed right.
Bros and roommates.
I'm going to be strict about this.
That means,
the first-and-last line,
'Just let everything take its natural course.'
After that, you can have
all kinds of actions,
but no talking allowed.
The words 'Jiang Xiaomeng' are off-limits.
No, I...
The first-and-last...
Then how do you pull it off?
Then you might
need to
reverse your order.
You can call his name at the start,
and only when you leave at the end,
do you say,
'Just let everything take its natural course.'
Actually, some lines in between don't need to be said.
The actions make things clear, right?
So what's the theme of this story?
I'd like to ask everyone.
I think it's parting before a long journey.
Parting.
Understand?
You need to know exactly what you're doing in this scene.
It feels like they're our sequel.
So we're your prequel.
Alright, next group.
Next group.
Get ready. Three, two, one.
Let's talk, okay?
What is there to talk about?
No matter what,
they're still our parents.
They're your parents.
They only love you, not me.
I'm begging you, as your brother.
Bye.
I'm about to tear up.
He's really crying.
Tears just streaming out.
Very good.
It's that simple.
Very clear.
The movements were organic too.
No need to give us any extra information.
Good, very good.
Alright, so today was just
our first acting class.
I'm very satisfied.
Including the scenes you performed later,
the emotional exercises and all.
So today's acting class ends here.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, madam.
Thanks for your hard work, madam.
Alright, students.
First, let's welcome,
our guest senior.
Gu Jiacheng.
Hello.
Hello, Senior.
I'm Gu Jiacheng.
I'm really happy to chat with you all today.
Today I'll just play games with you,
and everyone shares together.
Right, no need to be too formal.
And I still have one.
That...
that thing.
Well...
Because today,
the theme for us is 'you.'
It's about getting to know each other, and the process of getting acquainted.
So we hope, everyone takes off the makeup,
and then faces each other, directly, just as you are.
Right. So, who wants to go first?
You'll go first, right?
Is anyone here reluctant to remove their makeup?
Or is everyone okay with it?
I'm fine.
Everyone's okay with it?
Sure.
Okay with me.
Okay then.
Just kidding.
I've already wiped off the first stroke.
My personal take is
as actors, or whatever,
honestly, we all
don't need to focus too much on appearances.
Because everyone here is already good-looking.
Right.
No need to put so much thought and energy into it.
Better to focus on your inner self,
or on your own personal charm.
I think that would be better.
A good performer,
not only needs to know how to act,
but also how to observe.
This afternoon's first exercise,
is prepared just for you.
It's observation training.
The game is called 'Sensory Test'.
The two groups of students will observe each other.
Through each other's micro-expressions,
movements,
and acting,
find the one who's different.
For round one, our props are
three sets of massage insoles.
Among the four people, there's one,
who isn't wearing the insoles.
The group that's guessing,
can freely ask them
to perform any action.
You can use the small props coming up later together.
Now Group B, go to the next room and put on the insoles.
These are those insoles, right?
I think you can also do it like this.
There's a little ball under the ball of the foot.
That little ball.
Especially when you're standing on one foot like this...
It,
makes your center of gravity unstable.
So we can have them hold a bowl of water,
and then walk forward on their tiptoes,
and see how much spills.
Are you all acting like it hurts, or all acting like it doesn't?
Right now the main thing is
acting like it hurts, definitely,
the more over-the-top, the better.
Slow.
It hurts so bad.
Slowly.
Don't press on me.
Don't push.
His acting is a bit too fake.
So fake.
What if my foot cramps up?
My toes.
Slowly.
No good.
You guys are acting way too well.
This looks way too painful.
Chen Zhixuan definitely isn't.
The first student definitely isn't.
The first one is probably real.
I think the first one is probably real.
Okay, let's have one of us go first.
Come on.
Yes, stand on tiptoes on one foot,
and hold the water.
Five.
Four.
Then let's have Mingyang go.
Time to drink your water.
It must have been more than ten seconds.
Okay.
That's enough.
Honestly, my balance is
really not great.
Can I go on tiptoes?
Sure.
Actually, I just carefully observed everyone's feet,
because we know that
there's a ball up front,
so with a ball there, if you stand on tiptoes like that,
your center of gravity would be really unstable.
I paid special attention.
Actually Chen Zhixuan's forefoot is quite stable.
Because his foot is rather flat,
his foot can support him like that,
and he can put force into it.
But if there's a ball there,
he definitely couldn't use his strength.
He'd have to rely on his toes,
or the side of his foot,
to exert any force.
I think they can't know who it is,
but you're definitely Conan.
Such a good analyst.
Now expose each other.
I'll expose him, I'm reporting him. Do you believe it?
I do.
If you believe it, write it down.
If you believe it, just write it.
Give him the pen, sir.
Are you sure?
Answer.
Correct!
Amazing, over there!
Alright, now Group A
will experience the physiotherapy machine.
I bought one and use it at home every day.
Really?
He gets zapped every day, and has gotten used to it.
He knows its vibration frequency.
You use this yourself?
Yeah, it's really nice.
It's for physiotherapy.
Right, for physiotherapy.
They made really loud noises,
because they were testing it,
and kept screaming.
How come I feel nothing?
I thought I...
You okay?
No wait...
You got it on the muscle.
Got it on... on the muscle.
Don't put it on the bone.
I just zapped it over here.
You know what I mean?
Try the highest setting.
It feels amazing.
Seriously, it feels amazing. Give it a try.
You're treating it like a shock toy.
Give it a try.
I already tried it.
You tried it?
I tried it, but not on the highest setting.
I tried it. No, you try it.
Trust me, really.
No way.
Turn it off.
So if we're going to act it out,
we can only act out one muscle
twitching continuously at low frequency.
Then how about...
You do it.
He seems to have more knowledge about it.
Right.
Sure.
Then I'll do it.
You'll all have to bear with it.
How does it feel?
I really can't control it.
This thing really...
Wang Ruijian flinched.
Yeah, I think so.
It's definitely on.
Right.
You go first.
Start at level ten.
No.
I spelled out 'incomplete' with the Perler Beads.
And now we take turns going up,
each person adds a few beads to see if we can complete that 'incomplete'.
Sure.
Come on, let's do it.
Take a look.
Can we observe?
Of course you can.
See, I made this request on purpose.
So you're stuck either way,
whether to bead or not. Come on.
This one should be real.
I didn't feel him shaking.
Right, he should be real.
I think he's really trying to control his shaking.
So I think it's real.
This one is really hard.
This is so difficult.
Next one.
Next guest.
Pinch... no, this...
I really can't pinch it up.
Is it that intense?
How is it?
Yes.
It's on.
Okay.
Then I know now.
Right?
Which one is it?
Ma Weixian.
Let's hear from the physiotherapy machine master.
Answer.
Correct.
Let Senior experience it.
Then like this, let
Senior adjust the setting himself.
And we guess whether Senior turned it on or not,
and which setting it's on.
Sure, okay.
Can we do it like this?
Start it at three.
Let's observe.
Sure.
As the baseline.
Okay, now it's at three.
Looks like it's at three.
Okay?
Okay, come on.
Then I'll press it.
We won't look.
Turn around this way.
Okay.
It should be...
I feel like this one's pretty high.
No wait.
This one uses dedicated muscle effort.
So I think it's below level three.
I think it's pretty high and intense.
Level six or seven.
Six or seven, right?
I think it's around level five.
Can't really tell.
Right.
I think the he's acting was amazing.
I honestly kind of...
Great acting skills.
I wasn't acting.
It really is...
It really hurts.
Pick one.
Then I'll pick this one.
Either works.
What do you think?
I'll pick level six.
How many?
Level two, I think it's two.
Three, two, one, please reveal your answers.
Level two.
That's amazing.
That's such a good act.
That's incredible.
It's the transition process.
There's definitely a little pause.
And through that pause,
I guess it goes up first.
Then comes back down.
Because if it stayed at level five the whole time,
being above that for so long would be unbearable.
Right, you couldn't even press it.
So it must go up first.
Then come down during that pause.
I could tell from the sound.
That it must have gone down.
Then I saw that Senior's arm had marks from dedicated muscle effort.
And combined with what level three looked like.
The electrode twitching of this one wasn't as strong as level three.
So I think it should be level two.
You're so good at deducing.
They've got us beat.